

MUSTAPHA MBWANA RAMADHANI

Place of birth: Western town, Zanzibar

Marital status: Single

Gender: Male

Nationality: Tanzanian

Current location: Dar es salaam

Religion: Muslim

Contact: +255 715 969 193

About Me

I am a supremely motivated person with strong vision, enthusiasm and an unquenchable thirst to archive successful outcome. Proactive and capable of delivering excellent results while working under pressure with tight deadlines.

I am capable in System and information management with a year of experience completing private infrastructure projects. As a Data Professional, strong passion for developing Reports, Data Model, and Performance related Insights. Data analyst, Graphics design, IT Technician are the perfect fields for me. Comfortable working independently and as team and committed to provide highly-quality service with focus on health, safety and environmental issue. Possess Diploma in ICT.

EXPERIENCE

Organization: Clover Tanzania -Kito General Trading Company

Level: Junior

Location: Dar es salaam Tanzania

Position: Assistant System Admin and IT specialist

Date: 20th October 2021 to 31st December 2022

Responsibilities

❖ Monitoring sales system (Morpheus) and SAP business class in sales orders and invoice sides.

- ❖ Excel expertise, records management through internal system in the company.
- ❖ Preparation of reports as per request of the Management. Like sales analysis reports, Daily sales reports, stock reports branch wise.
- Software and Hardware maintenance.
- Troubleshooting and fixing minor faults in a Local area network.

Organization: EXCLUSIVE MOVIES AND GAMES

Level: Mid-level

Location: Dar es salaam Tanzania

Position: Operation supervisor and IT specialist

Date: 2nd Feb 2019-13th Oct 2021

Responsibilities

- ❖ Software and Hardware maintenance
- ❖ Installation of computer programs including operating systems and Games
- ❖ Monitoring and oversee daily activities in the office including selling movies, games and series to clients
- Provision of social Entertainment activities i.e. movies and games
- ❖ Prepare daily sales report to the top management

EDUCATION

✓ DIPLOMA IN COMPUTING AND INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

University: University of Dar es salaam Computing Centre (UCC)

Year: 2018 - 2020

Location: Dar es salaam

Award: 4.7/5.0 GPA (First Class)

✓ ADVANCED LEVEL SECONDARY EDUCATION

School: Ndanda High School

Year: 201-2016

Location: Mtwara in Masasi District

Award: Advanced Certificate of Secondary Education Examination

(ACSEE) 2016.

✓ ORDINARY LEVEL SECONDARY EDUCATION

School: King David Secondary School

Location: Mtwara

Award: Certificate of Secondary Education Examination (CSEE) 2013.

✓ PRIMARY EDUCATION

School: Mkomaindo Primary School

Location: Mtwara, Masasi

Award: Certificate of Primary Education 2009.

PROFFESIONAL SKILLS

- ❖ Microsoft Office and other Microsoft packages like Power BI, Microsoft SQL server
- System and Information Management
- Data Analysis tools (Analysis ToolPack)
- Basic Technician in Information and Communication Technology
- Full stuck developer using tools like PHP, MySQL database, CSS, and bootstrap
- CCNA (Cisco certified Network Associate)
- ❖ Graphics design specifics in adobe illustrator and Photoshop
- Basic Driving from Vocational Education and Training Authority (VETA)

HOBBIES AND INTEREST

- ❖ Watching movies and football is good since It helps to relax
- Playing PlayStation games
- ❖ Human Culture, establishing African arts and religion
- ❖ Learning new things specifically in technological improvement example python development in data management and analysis

REFEREERS

Mwanaisha Ali Maulid

Senior Economic Officer, Western Town Zanzibar

+255 773 306 372 mishamaulid@gmail.com

Fredrick Charles Mwedipando

Logic manager, Kito General Trading Company, Clover Tz

+255 768 085 153 Mwedy.fredy@gmail.com

Mudathir Khamis Ali

Private, JWTZ

🗘 +255 719 995 053 🖄 Mudathirkhamis1996@gmail.com